This is number one of five of my
favorite buy for life items. This is the
Happy Hacking Keyboard. This is a super
compact minimalist keyboard that has
been a staple in all of my workstations
in the past 10 plus years. This is the
keyboard that I learned how to touch
type on. And so I was able to increase
my typing speed to up to 180 words per
minute. It also forced me to learn
different keyboard shortcuts and that
has also helped with my productivity.
Compared to my MacBook whose keyboard I
don't even use that much. Within a few
months, there started to be this shine
on the keyboard plastic and it's
something very common that you see a lot
and that has not happened at all with
the Happy Hacking Keyboard even after 10
years of use. Only recently I decided to
try a upgraded version of the Happy
Hacking Keyboard which is the Happy
Hacking Keyboard Studio. And the only
difference with this new keyboard and
the previous one is that there is a
track point knob in the